We went through a lot of
all the former greats here first and
then around the league players that
we've been with different teams that we
were for and
kind of
narrowed down the qualities that they
all had and as we kind of narrowed it
down to the five things that we ended up
putting on the poster was
you know we all just looked at each
other and just it just screamed Lavonte.
So that was an easy for us to use
Lavonte as the
as the quote unquote poster child for
that so and he certainly embeds all of
that. You didn't draft him
but you resigned him and
This this has been a tough off season
for you Mike with Lavonte here. Can you
talk about
you becoming attached to these players
legends that you have helped either
draft and keep here in Tampa Bay that
won a Super Bowl here.
Especially when you have such a close
relationship with them
with Lavonte this is Lavonte's day. He
uh
you know I became very close with his
father. We had a Nebraska connection of
course with Lavonte but his dad was a
big Nebraska fan so he would talk with
me and my kids after the games and the
kids were all excited every time they
saw him.
Um
you know we saw each other every day. I
mean I told him on the phone the other
day when he told me
I said you know it's been awesome being
around greatness. It always is for the
12 years I've been here surround you
every day and I don't take any of that
for granted but
what's what's hard to say is it's I
can't believe that he's even better
person than he is a player and that says
a lot and I told him that
you know he's a role model not just for
what we look for in players but
you know I hope my my kids grow up to be
like him
and because he's just he just touches
everybody. It's he's got such a positive
outlook on things and he was definitely
raised right.
Jason having assessed so much talent
over the years like
the immeasurable the
the intangibles how rare is the makeup
of Lavonte David stats and football
side. It's
super rare. I mean I can only hope that
we drafted
player
like him again. It's hard. It's almost
impossible and
and
they did hats off to the organization
Mark Dominik and they got a they got an
outstanding one and then I was able to
reap the rewards of that here by giving
him 12 different contracts it seems
like. Told him on the stage I was hoping
to sign him to his 10th extension
whatever it is
uh when he called but
it's it's I mean it's it goes beyond
rare. It's
it's almost impossible but we'll
continue to try.
Anything else?
Thank you. Thanks guys.